[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'うります' read in word?",
        "answer": "Продавати"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しります' read in word?",
        "answer": "Знати"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'すみます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Проживати"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'けんきゅうします' read in word?",
        "answer": "Досліджувати"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しりょう' read in word?",
        "answer": "Документ"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'じこくひょう' read in word?",
        "answer": "Розклад"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'どくしん' read in word?",
        "answer": "Холостяк"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とこや' read in word?",
        "answer": "Перукарня (чоловіча)"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'びよういん' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "Салон краси, перукарня (жіноча)"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'じぶん' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "Власну"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the word 'プレイガイド' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "Театральна каса"
    }
]
